My lord, you guessed it right.
Ji Shuran did go
to see the Imperial Diviner.
First, a will-o'-the-wisp
outside Eldest Princess's Mansion,
then an exorcism at the Jiang Residence.
The Imperial Diviner
doesn't work
for the imperial court anymore.
Let's take them down
in one fell swoop then.
This is the map
of the Imperial Diviner Office.
I've sent our men to check it out.
My lord, Ms. Jiang Li has arrived.
My lord, Ms. Jiang Li is here.
Sorry to disturb you so late at night.
I didn't expect you to be busy
with official duties.
I'm sorry about that.
It's all right. We're just playing Go.
Are you interested in joining us, Li?
I'm here to ask for a favor,
so I can't stay long.
Another favor?
It's in your interest,
so it's not overstepping.
I'm all ears.
Do you want to get rid
of the Imperial Diviner, Duke Su?
Did you eavesdrop on us?
I came with your staff,
so I didn't have a chance
to eavesdrop on you.
But now it seems like
I've come at the right time.
Is it about the Jiang family's exorcism?
Yes, my stepmother persuaded my father
to invite the Imperial Diviner
for exorcism at our house.
I find this unusual.
She alone can't persuade
the Imperial Diviner to help her.
After much deliberation,
the only person I have offended
and can command the Imperial Diviner
is Eldest Princess Wanning.
The Imperial Diviner
is in charge of palace rituals.
This concerns the imperial family.
Now that he's working for someone else,
how can you stand by
and do nothing, Duke Su?
Brilliant.
Is that a yes?
State your request.
Get me someone who's good
at vocal mimicry and ventriloquism.
Is that it?
Yes.
- All right.
- Thank you.
I won't disturb you any longer.
I shall take my leave.
Li.
What did you say earlier?
What?
You said it'd be in my interest,
so it's not overstepping.
I know I owe you a lot.
I panicked a little,
so I tried to find an excuse.
I used to think
I could pay you back
everything I owed you.
Now that I've done the math,
I don't think I can pay you back.
Don't pay me back then.
You'll suffer losses.
I can afford it.
I'll get going then.
So the people
at the Imperial Diviner Office…
Withdraw them.
Yes.
But how can Ms. Jiang Li deal
with the whole
Imperial Diviner Office on her own?
It's all right.
If I can afford to lose,
she can too.
Ms. Jiang Li
has someone to support her now.
That's great.
Today, you'll be spared from flogging
as I'm in a good mood.
Are we all set for tomorrow?
Yes.
The Imperial Diviner
will arrive at 11:45 a.m.
When the time comes,
just put this pill into Ruoyao's mouth.
Keep a close eye on Concubine Hu.
Don't let her sabotage my plan.
Madam Ji,
I feel like the Imperial Diviner
is up to no good.
What should we do
if something goes wrong again?
What's there to worry about?
You're risking your life.
Do we have to go this far?
Jin Dai,
how many years have you been with me?
Since you were born,
it has been more than 30 years.
I've changed a lot
since then, haven't I?
Speak your mind.
Since you were a kid,
you've been the most
opinionated one in the family.
You also disobeyed your father the most.
But now,
you're becoming more and more like him.
Even you think I've changed,
don't you?
Madam Ji, actually, whatever you become
is the same to me.
I'll protect you no matter what.
But I don't want to see you unhappy.
I really miss
the eldest daughter of the Ji family,
who was carefree
and always had a smile on her face.
Once Jiang Li is out of the picture,
everything will be fine.
You must take care of yourself.
I shall take my leave.
SIMPLE AND ELEGANT
Miss, the person Duke Su got has arrived.
I've helped her change
into a maid's clothes.
She's with Bai Xue right now.
Remember to tell her
to stay close to me today.
Not too close, but not too far.
All right.
I think there will be a ruckus today.
I don't have time to watch over you.
Find a safe place.
Don't worry, miss.
I'm agile.
Come here.
Once this is over,
do you have any plans?
Actually, I'm quite tacky.
I just want to live
a life of comfort and luxury.
I don't want to live
like the old days in Zhennv Hall
when I didn't have enough
food to eat or clothes to keep warm.
What is this?
Open it and see.
Once this is over,
I'll be more than happy
if you choose to stay with me.
But now, you know how to read.
If you want to explore the world someday,
I have bought you a house in Luyang.
You can try to make a living
by running a small business.
If you want to marry someday,
just find a good man.
If you don't,
you'll be able to live a life
of comfort and luxury as you wish.
How could I deserve this?
Tong'er,
I've long thought of you
as my own younger sister.
Don't ever say that again.
Miss.
JIANG RESIDENCE
Greetings, Chancellor Jiang.
You're in charge of palace rituals.
Thank you for coming all the way here
for a trivial matter of my family.
Chancellor Jiang, you flatter me.
It all boils down to fate.
I came to Jiang Residence
to fulfill my destiny.
- Please come in.
- Chancellor Jiang, after you.
Is she Ms. Jiang Ruoyao?
Yes.
Evil spirits are born in the heart
and evil grudges take shape.
No shadow in a thousand years,
no root in the ages.
With summoning, you have nowhere to go.
Show yourself, you evil spirit!
Yao'er.
Yao'er!
- What's wrong with my daughter?
- Yao'er.
Ms. Jiang Ruoyao is possessed
by an evil spirit.
This evil spirit is so powerful
that it has almost
sucked out her vital qi.
If it can't be eliminated from the source,
her life will be in danger.
Imperial Diviner,
where is the evil spirit now?
Just now, I saw a dark haze
hovering over your residence at the door.
I'm afraid the evil spirit
is in the residence.
Nothing strange has ever happened
in this residence.
How can there be an evil spirit here
for no reason?
Imperial Diviner, are you mistaken?
Madam Ji, something big has happened.
The ancestral shrine is on fire.
Even the courtyard next door is on fire.
We must get rid of the evil spirit
as soon as possible.
If the evil spirit forms and invades,
more disasters will happen
to all of your family.
In serious cases,
you'll lose their lives.
Yao'er. Nothing can happen to my Yao'er.
Yao'er.
Imperial Diviner,
how do we exorcize the evil spirit?
The evil spirit needs a host.
Chancellor Jiang, please gather
everyone in the residence immediately.
I need to perform a ritual
and ask the spirit
to find the host.
The righteousness of the way of heaven
lets everything go back to its origin.
Water purifies,
spiritual talismans hold divine will.
Subdue evil spirits
and reveal their true forms.
All demons and monsters
could hide nowhere.
Demons and monsters?
It looks like a stunt to me.
Be quiet.
It's true.
I think so too.
It's said that the peach wood sword
can ward off evil spirits.
If there's really an evil spirit
in our residence,
it'll certainly be eliminated.
A wandering spirit
left the grave without permission.
A true shrine, a false disturbance.
The gates of heaven and earth have opened.
Lost soul, appear now!
- My lady!
- Jiang Li!
Imperial Diviner,
what's the meaning of this?
Chancellor Jiang,
this lady in the residence
is the host of the evil spirit.
This lady is possessed by an evil spirit.
If we don't get rid of it in time,
not only will it harm her,
but the entire Jiang family
will also be in chaos from now on.
Nonsense!
How can there be
an evil spirit in Ms. Jiang Li?
You're just slandering her.
What nonsense are you spouting?
How can Jiang Li be an evil spirit?
Li'er is usually very gentle and quiet.
She doesn't look like
an evil spirit's host.
Is there a misunderstanding here?
Imperial Diviner, you must be mistaken.
There can't be an evil spirit in Jiang Li.
Yes, Imperial Diviner.
Li'er lived in Zhennv Hall
on Qingcheng Mountain
for ten years.
Zhennv Hall is a pure place.
How can there be evil things?
You're wrong.
The tall trees
and thick grass in the mountains
are the most humid,
so they easily attracts evil spirits,
leading to evil thoughts.
Since this lady
stayed in Zhennv Hall before,
an evil spirit must have followed her.
And since her return, her mind
has gotten increasingly disturbed.
I'm afraid the reason lies
in Qingcheng Mountain.
You can say anything you want.
Why should we believe you?
Why should we just believe
whatever you say?
Mind your manners.
I was just telling the truth.
I'm sorry, Imperial Diviner.
We just don't understand it.
But Li'er
is a sensible and well-mannered
young lady of the Jiang family.
Please be more careful before judging her.
The personality of people
possessed by evil spirits
usually changes drastically.
May I ask if this lady's personality
has greatly changed
since her return?
Yes.
Ms. Jiang Li's personality and temperament
are completely different
after her return.
It's as if she's a different person.
- Yes.
- That's true.
I just feel sorry for Ms. Jiang Li,
who lived in Zhennv Hall for ten years.
When she was about to return
to Jiang Residence,
she was brutally murdered by someone.
I'm afraid even Ms. Jiang Li's father,
the Chief Secretariat,
is in the dark.
The Imperial Diviner is right.
A person's personality
can't change drastically
in a short period of time indeed.
But I left home and lived in Zhennv Hall
for not just a day or two,
not a month or two,
but ten years.
Ten years is not
a short period of time, is it?
If Mrs. Liu
hadn't met me in Zhennv Hall,
I'd still be kneeling there
for one whole day
without drinking a drop of water.
That was the norm in Zhennv Hall.
Not having enough food to eat
and clothes to keep warm,
getting beaten at every turn,
and not even allowed to beg for mercy.
With such a cycle,
even the most honorable and gentle woman
or the most innocent and naive child
won't have the same personality as before.
As for the habits mentioned earlier…
Father,
I've always loved meat,
soft quilts,
and brightly colored materials
for my clothes.
But in all my years in Zhennv Hall,
I've only had one quilt for my bed.
After using it for a long time,
all that's left are cotton scraps.
Forget colorful clothes.
Just being able to keep warm
is good enough.
If I were still as arrogant as before
and still insisted
on the same habits as before,
I might be dead already.
I changed
just to survive.
Did you hear that?
Jiang Li was forced by circumstances.
There's no such thing as an evil spirit.
What do you know?
Although evil spirits are bad,
they're spirits after all.
And if they're in a person's body
for a long time,
they will cultivate with their hosts,
capture their souls, master their skills,
and take shape.
They're not to be trifled with.
And they'll keep looking for new hosts
before they take shape.
Then they can take
the previous host's cultivation
with them.
Ms. Jiang Li is skilled
at playing the guqin
although she has never had a teacher.
And she surprised everyone
with her skill at the Annual Exam.
Perhaps this is the cultivation
brought by the evil spirit.
Besides,
Ms. Jiang Li risked her life
to overturn Magistrate Xue's conviction
and she looks very similar
to Magistrate Xue's daughter,
Xue Fangfei.
The last host of this evil spirit
was probably the late Xue Fangfei.
That's why I said
the reason for this
might lie in Qingcheng Mountain.
Everyone, think about it yourselves.
- Xue Fangfei? On Qingcheng Mountain?
- After Li'er
overturned Magistrate Xue's case,
she did not send him back to Huaixiang.
She even got him a physician
and some medicines.
She cares for him so much.
But before that, Li'er had no connection
with Xue Huaiyuan.
Why would she be
so concerned about an outsider?
Could it be true that…
Ms. Jiang Li,
have you ever encountered Xue Fangfei
and met her in person?
Of course I did.
I survived thanks to Xue Fangfei's help.
I'm grateful to her for saving my life.
It makes sense then!
That evil spirit
originally possessed Xue Fangfei
and did evil things.
After Xue Fangfei died,
it possessed Ms. Jiang Li.
This evil spirit is vicious and cunning.
If we don't get rid of it in time,
the entire Jiang family
might be in danger.
Father! Mother!
Ms. Ruoyao.
Yao'er.
Ruoyao.
- Mother!
- My daughter.
My Yao'er.
- Imperial Diviner.
- Mother!
What are you going to do
about the evil spirit in my daughter?
Your residence is not a pure place,
so I can't easily
suppress the evil spirit.
I need to take Ms. Jiang Li to the temple
to perform rituals for a few months
to get rid of the evil spirit.
Father!
Mother!
Chancellor Jiang,
you have to make up your mind soon.
If we wait until the evil spirit
completely takes over the body,
it'll be too late.
Yuanbai, you don't really believe
that an evil spirit
possessed Jiang Li, do you?
Uncle Yuanbai,
please don't believe in people's slander.
Jiang Li already suffered once
in Zhennv Hall.
If she suffers a second time,
- it will kill her.
- Yes.
My lord, Ms. Jiang Li is innocent.
There can't be any evil spirits
in our residence.
- Yuanbai, make a decision quickly.
- Yes, Yuanbai. Make a decision now.
You can't let our family
be destroyed like this.
- Or we can't live in peace, Yuanbai.
- Yes, Yuanbai.
Aunt Yang, what are you saying?
How could you say such nonsense?
- How is it nonsense?
- Enough!
Quiet!
Dear, what do you think?
Since the exorcism is harmless,
why don't we let the Imperial Diviner
take her back to check?
It's not like she won't be brought back.
Ruoyao is already in this state.
If anything happens to Jiang Li,
I won't be able to live on either.
Uncle Yuanbai!
Father!
Ms. Ruoyao.
I'm in so much pain!
Yao'er. My Yao'er.
Yao'er.
What should we do?
All right.
Jiang Li.
- Li'er.
- Jiang Li.
Li'er.
What's going on?
Ms. Jiang Li.
- Li'er.
- Jiang Li.
- Li'er, are you all right?
- Jiang Li, don't scare me.
Are you all right?
Jiang Li.
Li'er.
Father.
- Ms. Jiang Li.
- Father.
- Why's she like a different person?
- What's going on?
Father.
I feel so much pain.
- It hurts so much.
- Yue'er?
Yue'er.
- Imperial Diviner.
- Yue'er.
Jiang Li has been possessed
by an evil spirit.
Take her away!
Father.
Father, help me.
Let go of my Yue'er!
Let go of my daughter!
- Father.
- My Yue'er.
- Concubine Hu?
- Yue'er.
- Why is she here?
- I have no idea.
- My Yue'er.
My lord.
Don't you remember?
It's Yue'er's voice.
- It's Yue'er's voice.
- Yue'er.
Get someone to take her away. Quick.
- Yes. Guards.
- It's Yue'er.
Concubine Hu, come with me.
- No.
- Don't spout nonsense.
- Take her away. Don't spout nonsense.
- My lord.
Let go of me!
Father!
Yue'er.
That's our Yue'er.
- Father.
- Dear.
Father, help me.
Stop!
Stop, all of you.
Let go of her.
This concerns
my eldest granddaughter, Jiang Yue.
No one can leave
until we get to the bottom of this.
Old Madam, it's this crazy woman's doing.
- Ms. Sun, take her away.
- Yes.
Old Madam,
I'm really not crazy.
How could I not recognize
my own daughter's voice?
- Father.
- Old Madam.
- She's really Yue'er.
- Father, help me!
- My lord, listen.
Yue'er is calling you.
- Father. Father, help me!
- She's calling you.
Father!
- Yue'er.
- Dear.
Concubine Hu is really sick this time.
She's not sick.
This is Yue'er's voice.
It's our Yue'er.
Yue'er.
My Yue'er,
I'm sorry.
I feel so much pain.
Where does it hurt? Tell me.
My head hurts.
There's blood all over my head.
- My head hurts so much!
- Dear.
- Don't be afraid.
- All right.
Yue'er.
I won't dare to bully Ruoyao anymore.
Mother, don't push me.
My head hurts so much.
There's blood all over my head.
- Don't kill me!
- Don't be afraid.
Don't kill me!
- Nonsense!
- Don't kill me!
Jiang Li,
this is a trick of the evil spirit
to mesmerize people.
- You're the one who killed Yue'er.
- No!
- Don't be afraid, Yue'er.
- You killed my Yue'er!
Don't kill me.
My daughter was only eight years old.
Why did you kill her?
- Don't touch Madam Ji.
- Why?
- Don't be afraid.
Let go of me.
Let go!
Why?
- My lady.
- Jiang Li.
Father.
Grandmother.
The Imperial Diviner is really something.
I could really sense
something unseen.
Father,
I saw a little girl.
She said her name was Jiang Yue.
She begged me to apologize to her mother.
What exactly did you see?
I saw
Jiang Yue playing with Ruoyao.
Just because Ruoyao was crying,
Mother took it out on Jiang Yue
and pushed her.
Poor Jiang Yue died
after hitting her head on the rockery,
but someone made it look like
she accidentally fell and drowned.
Ji Shuran, you're so cruel!
My poor Yue'er
died at your hands.
My Yue'er!
My Yue'er.
Nonsense!
Jiang Li is possessed by an evil spirit.
Imperial Diviner!
Is this all you've got?
Take down the evil spirit!
They said Jiang Li
committed matricide and fratricide.
The mother was me
and the child she killed
was yours.
I was pregnant back then,
but she insisted
on taking me to the attic to play,
making me fall and lose the baby.
If it wasn't for her,
you and I
would still have a son.
And you
wouldn't have to live
in such loneliness and despair.
I've always wanted to avenge my child.
Don't you want to?
So will you
help me get rid of Jiang Li now?
Ms. Jiang Li's soul
has been seized by Xue Fangfei.
It must be exorcized immediately!
Miss, be careful!
The Imperial Diviner killed someone!
Let's go.
- Murder!
- Tong'er!
- He killed someone!
- No!
- Take him away!
- Old Madam.
Take Old Madam back to her room!
I…
- Jiang Li, run!
- Rui'er, do you want to die!
- Rui'er!
- Jiang Li, run! I'll fight you.
Li'er, run!
- Bai Xue, get a physician!
- Run!
All right.
Run, Jiang Li!
Jiang Li!
What…
- What do you want?
- Don't come near me!
Stay back!
If any of you come any closer,
I'll kill her!
Let's go.
Imperial Diviner.
Don't hurt Madam Ji.
Don't hurt Madam Ji!
Liu Wencai.
I'm so lucky.
Before I die,
you're the last person I see.
This is so nice.
You still owe me…
You owe me your life.
I'll find you
in my next life.
Wencai.
There are a lot of them.
- It's very inauspicious. It's so scary.
- Yes.
- It's so serious.
- How did something so bad happen? Look.
I haven't put away Shuran's stuff yet.
Let go of me!
Miss,
I'm sorry.
I can't be with you until the end.
The time I spent with you
was the happiest time of my life.
I want to meet you again
as your sister in the next life.
No.
Miss,
I'm glad
I'm finally going to her ladyship.
Tong'er.
Please
bury me next to her ladyship.
You're so beautiful.
You look the most beautiful
when you smile.
Don't cry.
I like to see your smile.
I won't cry.
Tong'er!
Don't take her away.
Tong'er.
You can't take her away.
You can't take her away!
Come back!
- Jiang Li.
- Tong'er.
Jiang Li.
- Jiang Li.
Don't go.
You can't take her away!
Tong'er!
Jiang Li.
Li'er!
Let her go!
The sooner she leaves,
the sooner she'll be reincarnated!
Tong'er!
No!
Jiang Li.
- Jiang Li.
- Tong'er!
Tong'er.
Tong'er, don't go.
I'm sorry.
Let's go with Madam Hu
to check out new fabrics today
and dress her up.
JI SHURAN ALSO KILLED YE ZHENZHEN
BECAUSE SHE WANTED TO MARRY
INTO THE JIANG FAMILY
Yue'er has finally redressed her justice.
I can feel at ease in meeting her now.
There's something
I've kept to myself for years.
Ji Shuran also killed
Ye Zhenzhen back then
because she wanted
to marry into the Jiang family.
The Imperial Diviner Office
knows the method of divination
and has a deep connection
with the inner court,
but it fell into the hands
of such a treacherous and evil person.
I've been unhappy
with the office for a long time.
Now that this has happened,
we can clean up and reorganize it.
Wanning would never have expected
that once Ms. Jiang Li joined the game,
all her chess pieces would be eliminated.
I guess we've made
the right bet this time.
Xue Fangfei,
just wait.
The best part is yet to come.